<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-02-18T00:37:52+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><title type="html">The Master’s University</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Burrito</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/news/burrito" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Burrito" /><published>2017-02-15T22:24:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-02-15T22:24:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/news/burrito</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/news/burrito">&lt;p&gt;kljasbkaljbflbflkq&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Michael</name></author><summary type="html">kljasbkaljbflbflkq</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/uploads/WEB_TMU.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Coffee</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/news/coffee" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Coffee" /><published>2017-02-13T22:15:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-02-13T22:15:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/news/coffee</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/news/coffee">&lt;p&gt;The Lord said to Abram, after Lot had separated from him, “Now lift up your eyes and look from the place where you are, northward and southward and eastward and westward; for all the land which you see, I will give it to you and to your descendants forever.” (Genesis 13:14-15)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Master’s University is a special place. Being built upon the foundation of God’s Word, having a faculty of the highest caliber and facilitating opportunities to foster friendships that will last a lifetime, very few schools can truly compete in offering a real, lasting education. Yet, a nondescript moshav (literally, “village” or “settlement”) tucked away in the Hill Country of Israel just may be Master’s University’s best-kept not-so-secret secret. This moshav, called Yad Hashmona, houses the campus of Master’s University’s Israel Bible Extension Program (or, as it is commonly called, IBEX). Conceived in the early 1990s in a conversation between Bill Schlegel (who still currently teaches at IBEX) and then-Master’s professor Doug Bookman, IBEX has soared in popularity with Master’s U students. As Dr. Varner has said so many times, “It’s not if you go to IBEX, but when you go to IBEX.” Indeed, every semester, 32 students are afforded an opportunity take part in this incredible program. This spring, I am blessed to be counted among that number. Over the next couple of months, I will be recounting some of the amazing experiences IBEX offers. Hopefully, you will catch a glimpse of what life is really like in the Promised Land!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YAD HASHMONA + KIRIATH-JEARIM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On January 29th around 8:30 AM, IBEX Spring 2017 boarded a bus that would begin our journey to Israel. With little sleep and little food, a stop at protest-riddled JFK and after hours of travel, we finally arrived around 4:30 PM (Israel Standard Time) on January 30th in Tel Aviv. Although we were all certainly feeling the effects of jet lag, “brimming with excitement” would better encapsulate our mood. After all, we stood on the precipice of three months of life in Israel! After a brief bus ride out of the Coastal Plain (Tel Aviv’s location) and into the Hill Country, we arrived at the settlement of Yad Hashmona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sure all of us on this trip would be willing to live virtually anywhere in Israel for the semester but residing at Yad Hashmona is a particular blessing. Our meals are eaten in a hotel restaurant, our linens and towels are washed weekly and many conveniences are within walking distance. Furthermore, all permanent residents of the moshav must profess faith in Jesus Christ. Interestingly, Israel’s government allows for this type of religious discrimination. For example, just down the road from Yad Hashmona is a settlement of Orthodox Jews. A predominantly Arab community of Abu Ghosh is also in close proximity to Yad Hashmona. Even the iconic Old City of Jerusalem just a few miles away is split into four distinct quarters comprised of Jews, Christians, Armenians and Muslims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directly to the east of Yad Hashmona stands the hilltop of Kiriath-Jearim. This past Wednesday, IBEX professor Benjamin Foreman led our group to explore this biblical site. This hilltop, referenced many times in the Old Testament, is perhaps best remembered for being the place that David stored the Ark of the Covenant for a short while (1 Sam. 7:1-2). Down the hill from Kiriath-Jearim stands the previously referenced city of Abu Ghosh. Abu Ghosh happens to be a prime candidate for the location of the biblical city of Emmaus (Luke 24:13-35). It was incredible to gaze at a site upon which Jesus likely walked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, a statue of Mary sits perched atop a church on Kiriath-Jearim. To me this statue, which overlooks Abu Ghosh and West Jerusalem, served as a reminder that many don’t yet know the coming King who will reign from this Jerusalem. Sadly, many in Israel are blinded to the reality of the Jewish Messiah. Whether it be a devout Orthodox Jew who insists that Jesus is not the Messiah, a Muslim who just acknowledges Jesus as another prophet, a “Christian” who is involved in a religious system that distorts the gospel of Christ or a secular Israeli who cares not for religion, all desperately need to know this Savior. May God use this semester’s IBEX team to be instruments to bring people to faith in Israel’s Messiah.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Michael</name></author><summary type="html">The Lord said to Abram, after Lot had separated from him, “Now lift up your eyes and look from the place where you are, northward and southward and eastward and westward; for all the land which you see, I will give it to you and to your descendants forever.” (Genesis 13:14-15)</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/uploads/TMUQuote%20copy.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Test</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/news/test" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Test" /><published>2017-01-31T01:15:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-01-31T01:15:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/news/test</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/news/test">&lt;p&gt;When it comes to matters of objective truth, like the Gospel, this world has effectively encouraged an ecumenical faith that embraces “all truths” as equal.  Our culture virtually prickles at the thought of objective, absolute truth, particularly when it comes to a person’s faith.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, this mindset is widespread and I’ve found myself dancing around the truth so not to offend.  Without intending to, I’m actually muddying the contrast between right and wrong, the honest truth and a sly lie.  True unity and peace only come from understanding and believing the truth.  We shouldn’t forget that the truth comes from God; it’s not “our truth.” We didn’t find it or invent it.  Truth has always been found outside of us in the pages of Scripture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s powerful when we fully embrace the truth and are blessed with peace and unity with the body of Christ.  The Gospel message gives hope that our eternal salvation depends not on our good works or religious tradition but on the perfect work of Jesus.  We should be confident when we talk about this because our authority is the divine Word of God.  We must overcome the natural temptation to make our Christian faith about us and our opinions.  It’s also important to be reminded that the Holy Spirit has to work in the hearts of the hearer before he can change.  We should be faithful to proclaim the truth but we aren’t the ones responsible for changing hearts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully most of us living in America haven’t had to worry about persecution like our brothers and sisters do in China, Russia and many of the Arab countries, to name a few.  Our Christian life is one of relative comfort and ease, especially if we stay tucked inside our safe-zones.  However, we are warned that if we live faithfully according to the Bible, it won’t be long until we aren’t invited or welcome in certain social circles, as we’re reminded in 2 Timothy 3:12 “Yes, and all who desire to live godly in Christ Jesus will suffer persecution.”  Maybe we won’t be arrested or sent to jail but we will suffer rejection.  Jesus himself promised us that a servant is not greater than his master in John 15:20.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a current trend to “find your path” or to “embrace your journey.”  As a Christian mom of three young sons, my husband and I teach our boys the truth and principles from the Bible, as we’re called to do.  Recently, I was having a friendly discussion with some other moms about how we each approach teaching our faith to our kids and they all seemed to agree on the answer.  They said that they don’t like to tell Johnny what to believe or where to look, they expose him to a little bit of everything and their hope is that he’ll pick what’s right for him down the line.  What a sad, vague path to a personal truth that ultimately can’t save.  Parents are hoping their kids will find some kind of subjective truth that they’ll feel comfortable enough to live with.  Whatever they find, mixed with some sincerity, is good enough.  It’s silly, if it weren’t so sad.  It’s as though discovering the truth is not unlike visiting Baskin-Robbins and picking out a favorite flavor from the 31 offered!  Sadly, the “whatever tastes good to you” method isn’t enough when it comes to finding the real truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The underlying, subtle lie is this: you can choose to believe what you want and if you’re sincere and behave in an acceptable way in society you’re set.  This is the type of faith that Jesus warned about in Matthew 7: 13-14, “Enter through the narrow gate; for the gate is wide and the way is broad that leads to destruction, and there are many who enter through it.  For the gate is small and the way is narrow that leads to life, and there are few who find it.”    &lt;br /&gt;
We send our kids to school to learn facts.  We don’t expect the teachers to explain away physical laws and mathematical or grammar rules in favor of how the child feels about those principles.  We all acknowledge that scientific and math realities are true and aren’t up for discussion; there is no room for personal feelings about these facts!  We expect our kids to come out knowing objective facts.  So why does the world feel it ok to pick “your truth” according to personal feelings?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“True religion” has to be anchored in truth.  In our vain attempts to offend no one we have failed to love them.  Jesus made people uncomfortable; he made the local religious people very uncomfortable.  It’s not easy to stand up and be different when you’re in a group that doesn’t hold to or even know or care about Bible truth.  We are reminded what 1 Corinthians 1:18 says: “For the message of the cross is foolishness to those who are perishing, but to us who are being saved it is the power of God.”  But if the truth is worth believing then it’s worth defending and it’s worth sharing!  Many of our conversations would be so much easier if we knew our Bible better.  I love the truth and I love hearing the truth, but if my mind can’t recall the many promises and if my lips never share the truth with others, then who am I helping, who am I loving?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you are identified as a Christian, and not just “a good neighbor” then there’s a target on your back.  Once you hold to the objective truth that originates from the Bible, there’s an even bigger target on your back.  1 Peter 3:15 reminds us of our high calling: “always be ready to give a defense to everyone who asks you a reason for the hope that is in you, with meekness and fear.”  Friends, we need to be encouraged to share the hope that is in us so that others might be saved.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">When it comes to matters of objective truth, like the Gospel, this world has effectively encouraged an ecumenical faith that embraces “all truths” as equal.  Our culture virtually prickles at the thought of objective, absolute truth, particularly when it comes to a person’s faith.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/uploads/WelcomeWeb3.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">TMU</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/news/TMU" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TMU" /><published>2017-01-31T01:15:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-01-31T01:15:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/news/TMU</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/news/TMU">&lt;p&gt;When it comes to matters of objective truth, like the Gospel, this world has effectively encouraged an ecumenical faith that embraces “all truths” as equal.  Our culture virtually prickles at the thought of objective, absolute truth, particularly when it comes to a person’s faith.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, this mindset is widespread and I’ve found myself dancing around the truth so not to offend.  Without intending to, I’m actually muddying the contrast between right and wrong, the honest truth and a sly lie.  True unity and peace only come from understanding and believing the truth.  We shouldn’t forget that the truth comes from God; it’s not “our truth.” We didn’t find it or invent it.  Truth has always been found outside of us in the pages of Scripture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s powerful when we fully embrace the truth and are blessed with peace and unity with the body of Christ.  The Gospel message gives hope that our eternal salvation depends not on our good works or religious tradition but on the perfect work of Jesus.  We should be confident when we talk about this because our authority is the divine Word of God.  We must overcome the natural temptation to make our Christian faith about us and our opinions.  It’s also important to be reminded that the Holy Spirit has to work in the hearts of the hearer before he can change.  We should be faithful to proclaim the truth but we aren’t the ones responsible for changing hearts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully most of us living in America haven’t had to worry about persecution like our brothers and sisters do in China, Russia and many of the Arab countries, to name a few.  Our Christian life is one of relative comfort and ease, especially if we stay tucked inside our safe-zones.  However, we are warned that if we live faithfully according to the Bible, it won’t be long until we aren’t invited or welcome in certain social circles, as we’re reminded in 2 Timothy 3:12 “Yes, and all who desire to live godly in Christ Jesus will suffer persecution.”  Maybe we won’t be arrested or sent to jail but we will suffer rejection.  Jesus himself promised us that a servant is not greater than his master in John 15:20.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a current trend to “find your path” or to “embrace your journey.”  As a Christian mom of three young sons, my husband and I teach our boys the truth and principles from the Bible, as we’re called to do.  Recently, I was having a friendly discussion with some other moms about how we each approach teaching our faith to our kids and they all seemed to agree on the answer.  They said that they don’t like to tell Johnny what to believe or where to look, they expose him to a little bit of everything and their hope is that he’ll pick what’s right for him down the line.  What a sad, vague path to a personal truth that ultimately can’t save.  Parents are hoping their kids will find some kind of subjective truth that they’ll feel comfortable enough to live with.  Whatever they find, mixed with some sincerity, is good enough.  It’s silly, if it weren’t so sad.  It’s as though discovering the truth is not unlike visiting Baskin-Robbins and picking out a favorite flavor from the 31 offered!  Sadly, the “whatever tastes good to you” method isn’t enough when it comes to finding the real truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The underlying, subtle lie is this: you can choose to believe what you want and if you’re sincere and behave in an acceptable way in society you’re set.  This is the type of faith that Jesus warned about in Matthew 7: 13-14, “Enter through the narrow gate; for the gate is wide and the way is broad that leads to destruction, and there are many who enter through it.  For the gate is small and the way is narrow that leads to life, and there are few who find it.”    &lt;br /&gt;
We send our kids to school to learn facts.  We don’t expect the teachers to explain away physical laws and mathematical or grammar rules in favor of how the child feels about those principles.  We all acknowledge that scientific and math realities are true and aren’t up for discussion; there is no room for personal feelings about these facts!  We expect our kids to come out knowing objective facts.  So why does the world feel it ok to pick “your truth” according to personal feelings?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“True religion” has to be anchored in truth.  In our vain attempts to offend no one we have failed to love them.  Jesus made people uncomfortable; he made the local religious people very uncomfortable.  It’s not easy to stand up and be different when you’re in a group that doesn’t hold to or even know or care about Bible truth.  We are reminded what 1 Corinthians 1:18 says: “For the message of the cross is foolishness to those who are perishing, but to us who are being saved it is the power of God.”  But if the truth is worth believing then it’s worth defending and it’s worth sharing!  Many of our conversations would be so much easier if we knew our Bible better.  I love the truth and I love hearing the truth, but if my mind can’t recall the many promises and if my lips never share the truth with others, then who am I helping, who am I loving?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you are identified as a Christian, and not just “a good neighbor” then there’s a target on your back.  Once you hold to the objective truth that originates from the Bible, there’s an even bigger target on your back.  1 Peter 3:15 reminds us of our high calling: “always be ready to give a defense to everyone who asks you a reason for the hope that is in you, with meekness and fear.”  Friends, we need to be encouraged to share the hope that is in us so that others might be saved.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Blake Noll</name></author><summary type="html">When it comes to matters of objective truth, like the Gospel, this world has effectively encouraged an ecumenical faith that embraces “all truths” as equal.  Our culture virtually prickles at the thought of objective, absolute truth, particularly when it comes to a person’s faith.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/uploads/WEB_TMU.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The University Exchange</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/news/the-university-exchange" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The University Exchange" /><published>2017-01-31T00:56:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-01-31T00:56:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/news/the-university-exchange</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/news/the-university-exchange">&lt;p&gt;A bookstore is a physical representation of an institution; it represents who we are. October 2016 The Master’s University Bookstore closed its doors and was cleared out for renovation. Paper covered the windows and thin wood walls concealed the facade — hiding the work being done, but unable to silence the sound of nails being hammered in or stifle the smell of fresh paint.
On February 3rd the mystery will be revealed. The walls will come down and the students, faculty, staff, visitors and greater community will be welcomed to the new University Exchange, or UE for short.
“This is one of the first big things that’s happened for the students in a while,” Robert Jensen of University Marketing said, “the University Exchange represents them. The students are the priority. You won’t recognize it from the old bookstore. The exterior framework did not change but the interior space was completely re-designed. The entire process has been an alumni effort as well, with the designers and general contractor all being graduates of Master’s U.”
The change from college to university took place in early August and represents more than a lexical difference. It is an exciting step in not only highlighting the unique strengths already present here, but also elevating the standards and expectations by which the university functions.  The bookstore is only one step in the means to a greater end.
Jensen explained, “UE will no longer simply fill a need but create an experience. . . an experience that immediately fills students and alumni with a sense of pride in their university — the moment you walk into this place you are going to feel a part of the school and actually want to represent it outside of the canyon.”
There will be an entire section featuring the collected works of our president, Dr. John MacArthur, along with shelves filled with classic literature recommended by the English faculty, books suggested by the Business and History departments, biographies, entrepreneurial and more. The latter offered are all supplemental to the course textbooks students will be able to purchase online (ue.masters.edu).
However, UE will not only have books. Emily Clark, a senior Biblical Counseling major at Master’s U, commented, “It’s exciting because the staff is putting a lot of work into giving it a whole new look. It will be ivy league and collegiate, perhaps more so than any other university. It’s exciting to make our school presentable to people. Merchandise sells a school to high schoolers; when something looks nice it will bring people in.”
The University Exchange is more than books or merchandise. Everything about the store — the design, books, atmosphere, product and even the team behind it —- brings together the past, present and future of The Master’s University. The UE will offer multiple generations of students and guests the opportunity to take a piece of the university with them, united under one cohesive identity.
We cannot wait for you, along with the Master’s U Board of Directors, to join us at The University Exchange for it’s official opening next Friday, February 3rd at 12 noon!&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">A bookstore is a physical representation of an institution; it represents who we are. October 2016 The Master’s University Bookstore closed its doors and was cleared out for renovation. Paper covered the windows and thin wood walls concealed the facade — hiding the work being done, but unable to silence the sound of nails being hammered in or stifle the smell of fresh paint.
On February 3rd the mystery will be revealed. The walls will come down and the students, faculty, staff, visitors and greater community will be welcomed to the new University Exchange, or UE for short.
“This is one of the first big things that’s happened for the students in a while,” Robert Jensen of University Marketing said, “the University Exchange represents them. The students are the priority. You won’t recognize it from the old bookstore. The exterior framework did not change but the interior space was completely re-designed. The entire process has been an alumni effort as well, with the designers and general contractor all being graduates of Master’s U.”
The change from college to university took place in early August and represents more than a lexical difference. It is an exciting step in not only highlighting the unique strengths already present here, but also elevating the standards and expectations by which the university functions.  The bookstore is only one step in the means to a greater end.
Jensen explained, “UE will no longer simply fill a need but create an experience. . . an experience that immediately fills students and alumni with a sense of pride in their university — the moment you walk into this place you are going to feel a part of the school and actually want to represent it outside of the canyon.”
There will be an entire section featuring the collected works of our president, Dr. John MacArthur, along with shelves filled with classic literature recommended by the English faculty, books suggested by the Business and History departments, biographies, entrepreneurial and more. The latter offered are all supplemental to the course textbooks students will be able to purchase online (ue.masters.edu).
However, UE will not only have books. Emily Clark, a senior Biblical Counseling major at Master’s U, commented, “It’s exciting because the staff is putting a lot of work into giving it a whole new look. It will be ivy league and collegiate, perhaps more so than any other university. It’s exciting to make our school presentable to people. Merchandise sells a school to high schoolers; when something looks nice it will bring people in.”
The University Exchange is more than books or merchandise. Everything about the store — the design, books, atmosphere, product and even the team behind it —- brings together the past, present and future of The Master’s University. The UE will offer multiple generations of students and guests the opportunity to take a piece of the university with them, united under one cohesive identity.
We cannot wait for you, along with the Master’s U Board of Directors, to join us at The University Exchange for it’s official opening next Friday, February 3rd at 12 noon!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/news/welcome-to-jekyll" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2017-01-12T21:51:59+00:00</published><updated>2017-01-12T21:51:59+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/news/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/news/welcome-to-jekyll">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/" /></entry></feed>
